Ahmed Mansour

Civil Engineer with +7 Years Experience and have a deep passion for Computer Science. Experienced in site engineering and project coordination. Skilled in programming and software development, with completed projects in Python, Flask, and SQL.

Skills

Design & Drafting Software

· AutoCAD, Civil 3D, Revit And other Surveying Programs.

Programming Languages:

- · Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL.
- · Flask, API Integration, Database Management.

Work Experience

Site Engineer

Farag Sultan Contracting and Transportation Establishment

Jun 2021 - Jun 2023

- Managed the installation of interlock pavement and asphalt roads, ensuring quality standards.
- Coordinated and executed substitution layers for multiple roads and roundabouts.
- Ensured compliance with project deadlines and quality control.

Consulting Engineer

Housing And Building National Research Center

Jul 2020 - May 2021

- Supervised carpentry, metalwork, and concrete construction activities.
- Conducted quality control inspections for residential zones.
- Managed construction activities and ensured compliance with safety regulations.

Executive Engineer

El-Masrawyah Building & Construction

Mar 2019 - May 2020

- · Led engineering-related project activities and coordinated with stakeholders.
- Supervised daily construction activities to meet engineering specifications.

Executive Engineer

Al-Maraj Building & Construction

Apr 2018 - Feb 2019

- Maintain accurate records of progress, daily reports, and any issues encountered on-site and prepare periodic progress reports for senior management and stakeholders.
- Directed design and construction of various foundation types, including slab-on-grade, deep foundations, and pile foundations for residential, commercial, and industrial buildings.

Contact

Cairo, Egypt +20 - 100 9069 364 nabilahmed0100@gmail.com Github | Portfolio | Linkedin

Education

Degree:

Bachelor of Civil Engineering

University Name:

Higher Institute of Engineering and Technology in Kafr El Sheikh